<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by crowdin.com-->
<!--
  ~ Piwigo for Android
  ~ Copyright (C) 2019-2019 Valentin Baizeau https://voriondev.fr
  ~ Copyright (C) 2018-2019 Raphael Mack http://www.raphael-mack.de
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016-2018 Piwigo Team http://piwigo.org
  ~
  ~ This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with this program.  If not, see <https://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Piwigo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Innlogging</string>
    <string name="title_activity_accounts">Administrer kontoer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">Om</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Innstillinger</string>
    <string name="title_select_image">Velg bilde</string>
    <!-- Navigation drawer menu items -->
    <string name="nav_icon_description">Piwigo-logo</string>
    <string name="nav_server_version">Tjenerversjon: %1$s</string>
    <string name="nav_albums">Album</string>
    <string name="nav_upload">Last opp</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Innstillinger</string>
    <string name="nav_logout">Logg ut</string>
    <string name="nav_add_account">Legg til konto</string>
    <string name="nav_delete_account">Fjern konto</string>
    <string name="nav_edit_account">Endre konto</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_open">Åpne navigasjonsmeny</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_close">Lukk navigasjonsmeny</string>
    <!-- Login -->
    <string name="login_url_hint">Tjeneradresse</string>
    <string name="login_url_empty">Angi tjeneradressen din</string>
    <string name="login_url_invalid">Ikke en gyldig tjeneradresse</string>
    <string name="login_username_empty">Angi brukernavnet ditt</string>
    <string name="login_username_hint">Brukernavn (tom for gjest)</string>
    <string name="login_button_description">Logg inn</string>
    <string name="login_password_empty">Angi passordet ditt</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Passord (tom for gjest)</string>
    <string name="login_error">Innlogging feilet</string>
    <string name="login_account_error">En konto for denne serveren eksisterer allerede</string>
    <string name="login_ssl_error">Kryptert tilkobling (SSL) til \'%1s\' kunne ikke etableres</string>
    <string name="login_host_error">Tjeneren \'%1s\' kunne ikke nås, vennligst sjekk adressen</string>
    <string name="login_http_error">Tjeneren ga et uventet svar \'%1s\'</string>
    <string name="login_http_404_error">Angitt filsti \'%1s\' ble ikke funnet på tjeneren</string>
    <string name="login_baseurl_invalid">Intet Piwigo-galleri funnet på den oppgitte filstien \'%1s\'</string>
    <string name="login_invalid_credentials">Innlogging feilet med den gitte brukerinformasjonen \'%1s/*****\'</string>
    <!-- Account -->
    <string name="account_image_description">Snarvei-ikon for galleriet (favicon)</string>
    <string name="account_not_selected">Velg en konto som skal slettes først</string>
    <string name="account_empty_message">Tom konto!</string>
    <string name="account_logout_successful">Utlogging var vellykket!</string>
    <string name="account_logout_unsuccessfull">Utlogging feilet: %1$s</string>
    <!-- About -->
    <string name="about_text_version">versjon <b>%1$s</b></string>
    <string name="about_text_intro"> - få tilgang til Piwigo-gallerier fra Android-enheten din.</string>
    <string name="about_text_licence_h">Lisens</string>
    <string name="about_text_licence"><![CDATA[%1$s er gratis programvare: du kan redistribuere det og/eller endre det under vilkårene av <a href="https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.en.html">GNU General Public License</a>]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_license_2">Dette programmet distribueres med håp om at det kan være nyttig, men UTEN NOEN GARANTI; også uten den antydde garantien gitt av VAREMERKET eller BRUKBARHETEN FOR ET SPESIELT FORMÅL. Se GNU General Public License for flere detaljer.</string>
    <string name="about_text_privacy_h">Personvern</string>
    <string name="about_text_privacy"><![CDATA[%1$s og dens utviklere har stor interesse i å respektere privatlivet ditt. Derfor er denne appen designet for å ikke spore bruken din av appen og holde dine data i dine hender. Det er anbefalt å sette opp ditt eget Piwigo-galleri med din egne lokale tjener og bare bruke krypterte koblinger via HTTPS. Les hele <a href=\"org.piwigo.privacy_policy://show\">personvernerklæringen</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_contact_h">Kontakt</string>
    <string name="about_text_contact"><![CDATA[For feil eller forslag til appen, bruk <a href="https://github.com/Piwigo/Piwigo-Android/issues">feilsøkeren</a>, helst på Engelsk.]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_contact_2"><![CDATA[Kildekoden finnes på <a href="https://github.com/Piwigo/Piwigo-Android">Github</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_contact_3"><![CDATA[Diskusjoner burde ta plass i <a href="https://piwigo.org/forum/">Piwigo-forumet</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_contact_4"><![CDATA[For alt du vil fortelle oss privat, send en e-post til <a href="mailto:android@piwigo.org">android@piwigo.org</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_support_h">Bidra</string>
    <string name="about_text_support"><![CDATA[I tilfellet du har lyst til å støtte utviklingen av %1$s, vurder å diskutere <a href="https://github.com/Piwigo/Piwigo-Android/issues">feil på GitHub</a> eller ved å sende inn <a href="https://github.com/Piwigo/Piwigo-Android/pulls">Pull Requests</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="about_text_ack_h">Anerkjennelser</string>
    <string name="about_text_ack_2">Vi ser frem til å nevne deg i denne lista også.</string>
    <string name="about_text_lib_h">Ressurser</string>
    <string name="about_text_lib">De følgene ressursene brukes av denne applikasjonen og er lisensert under de nevnte lisensene:</string>
    <!-- Albums -->
    <plurals name="album_photos">
        <item quantity="one">1 bilde</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d bilder</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="album_photos_subs">
        <item quantity="one">, 1 bilde i underalbum</item>
        <item quantity="other">, %1$d bilder i underalbum</item>
    </plurals>
    <!-- Privacy Policy -->
    <string name="privacy_text">Piwigo-Android and Piwigo-Mobile are free, libre and open source client applications for Piwigo galleries. This privacy policy applies to these native Android and iOS applications, connecting to Piwigo sites which are out of the control of the authors. Check the privacy policy of the corresponding sites before configuring an account in Piwigo-Android or Piwigo-Mobile to connect to a gallery.</string>
    <string name="privacy_last_update">Last updated October 25, 2018</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_text1">Developers of Piwigo-Android and Piwigo-Mobile, we (or “us” or “our”) respect the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you use our mobile applications (the “Applications”). Our names can be extracted from the meta data in the git repositories and within the Applications.</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_text2">Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not access the Applications.</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_text3">We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last updated” date of this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_text4">You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Applications after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.</string>
    <string name="privacy_intro_text5">This Privacy Policy does not apply to the third-party online/mobile store from which you install the Applications or make payments, including any in-app virtual items, which may also collect and use data about you. We are not responsible for any of the data collected by any such third party.</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_title">What data is processed and stored?</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subTitle1">Piwigo Gallery Data</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subText1a">Account credentials are stored by the Applications and submitted to the configured sites to connect to one or several Piwigo galleries. Beside that, all the photos, videos and other files that are selected for download/upload and the entered content is stored, processed and transmitted to the configured gallery site.</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subTitle2">Geo-Location Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subText2a">We may request access or permission to and track location-based information from your mobile device, either continuously or while you are using the Applications, to provide location-based services. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subTitle3">Mobile Device Access</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subText3a">The Applications may request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s photo library and file storage, the Android AccountManager, the Apple Keychain, foreign and cloud based storage folders, geolocalisation, and other features. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings but be aware that some accesses are necessary to upload media files of your mobile to the Piwigo gallery or to store Piwigo media files in your mobile.</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subTitle4">Mobile Device Data</string>
    <string name="privacy_what_subText4a">When contacting the support team, device information such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer, version of your operating system, email, country, location, and any other data you choose to provide may be transmitted to the development team of the Applications. Beside the data explicitly shared by the user with the developers no content will be stored, transmitted or processed by us.</string>
    <string name="privacy_why_title">Why does the mobile app store data?</string>
    <string name="privacy_why_text1">The Applications store only data to satisfy one intention: accessing a Piwigo gallery hosted on a foreign webserver. No data is collected, transmitted or stored that is not required for its intended functionality.</string>
    <string name="privacy_why_text2">When you access the Applications, your personal information is not collected through the use of tracking technology. We only use caching mechanisms to help customize the Applications and improve your experience. You can disable or clear caches, but be aware that such action could affect the availability and functionality of the Applications.</string>
    <string name="privacy_how_title">How is the data protected?</string>
    <string name="privacy_how_text1">The Applications store data locally on the device it is executed on. You are responsible to protect the stored data from unauthorized access. We strongly recommend to use HTTPS to protect data during transmission and the Applications try to use HTTPS the first time the user establishes a connection with a Piwigo gallery. Keeping certificates and libraries for HTTPS access up to date is under responsibility of the Piwigo server operator. When the Applications cannot use HTTPS, they switches to HTTP and data are not encrypted during transmission.</string>
    <string name="privacy_how_text2">When you upload images to a Piwigo gallery, images may contain private data like GPS coordinates or comments. The Applications provide an option for removing these data from image files before upload in the Settings section. It is the responsibility of the user to decide whether those private data are uploaded.</string>
    <string name="privacy_security_title">Security of your information</string>
    <string name="privacy_security_text">We use technical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information.</string>
    <string name="privacy_contact_title">Contact us</string>
    <string name="privacy_contact_text">If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:</string>
    <string name="privacy_contact_address">Piwigo, 42 rue des Vignes, 21800 Quetigny (France)</string>
    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="settings_albums_title">Albums</string>
    <string name="settings_download_size">Download Size</string>
    <string name="settings_images">Images</string>
    <string name="settings_photos_per_row">Photos per Row</string>
    <string name="settings_download_size_summary">Photo size \'%1$s\' will be used for download</string>
    <!-- Upload -->
    <string name="upload_success">Upload successful</string>
    <string name="upload_failed">Upload failed</string>
    <string name="upload_error">An error occurred while upload your photo(s). Please try again.</string>
    <string name="upload_progress_body">Uploaded %1$d / %2$d photos</string>
    <string name="upload_started">Uploading your photos</string>
    <string name="upload_success_body">Uploaded %1$d photo(s) to %2$s</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_title">Missing permissions.</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_explanation">Uploading photos is only possible if you give access to the storage.</string>
    <!-- Album created -->
    <string name="create_album_title">Create album</string>
    <string name="create_album_success">Album %1$s created.</string>
    <string name="create_album_error">Unable to create album.</string>
    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="button_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_report">Report</string>
    <!-- FAB -->
    <string name="fab_create_album">Create album</string>
    <string name="fab_create_subalbum">Create sub-album</string>
    <string name="fab_upload_photos">Upload photos</string>
    <!-- ACRA crash reporting -->
    <string name="crash_dialog_text">An unexpected error occurred forcing the application to stop. Please help us fix this by sending us error data, all you have to do is click OK and send the email that we prepared.</string>
    <string name="crash_dialog_comment_prompt">You might add your comments about the problem below:</string>
    <!-- Not implemented -->
    <string name="not_implemented_title">Not implemented yet.</string>
    <string name="not_implemented_msg">This feature has not been implemented yet!</string>
    <!-- Guest error messages-->
    <string name="not_admin">Not logged in</string>
    <string name="not_admin_explanation">You need to be logged to do this.</string>
    <string name="no_internet">Oops! It seems like you have no internet connection. Please connect and try again.</string>
    <string name="show_details">Show details</string>
    <!-- Spinner Download Size array-->
    <string-array name="download_size_array">
        <item>square</item>
        <item>thumb</item>
        <item>small</item>
        <item>medium</item>
        <item>large</item>
        <item>xxlarge</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
